Finding Aid for Jeep Holland papers, 1943-1998
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Jeep Holland papers
1943-1998
Holland, Jeep, 1943-1998.
2009082 Aa 2
Hugh "Jeep" Holland was the founder of the A-Square Record label in Ann Arbor in 1967, and consequently became an integral part of the southeast Michigan music scene in the late 1960s and early 1970s. The collection documents, in papers, photographs and sound recordings, Jeep’s personal life, interests, and career.
12 linear feet in 13 boxes
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
The papers were donated to the library by Francis Holland, (donor no. 9973 ) in 2008.
No further additions to the papers are expected.
The collection is open to research.
Hugh Henry "Jeep" Holland was born in 1943 in Boston, Massachusetts. Stories explaining the origin of his nickname stem from his father's work during World War II, and vary between working with the motor pool, and working in the Studebaker factory that was then manufacturing Jeeps for the war effort. Following the war, the Holland family moved to East Lansing, Michigan, where Jeep and his younger brother, Frank Jr. (sometimes called "Jomp"), grew up and attended school.
During school, Jeep participated in a number of extracurricular activities including student council, various theatrical productions, and the wrestling and football teams. It was also during his youth that Jeep developed interests that would guide his later career path. Jeep's habitual collecting likely started at a very young age. He accumulated comic books, promotional materials for his favorite cartoons and movies, and created detailed scrapbooks of important events in his life. Likewise, as a child, Jeep was a talented violinist. While he apparently didn't particularly enjoy the instrument, his love of music was beyond question, and by the time he was 16, he was essentially running the local record store. This position at the record store also contributed to his collecting impulses, as he made a point of acquiring popular records as they were released. Furthermore, Jeep's work at the record store and his extensive knowledge of popular music provided him with his first tastes of the music scene that he would soon become an integral part of, as he acted as DJ for local dances and other events.
Following his graduation from high school in 1961, Jeep moved to Ann Arbor, Michigan, to continue his education at the University of Michigan. Jeep mainly focused on humanities courses, and while he occasionally excelled in his school work, he was inconsistent enough that by January of 1966, he was asked by the university not to enroll in classes for the following semester.
Though his studies were unsuccessful, Jeep had taken a manager position at the Ann Arbor branch of Discount Records, and was quickly becoming a fixture of the Ann Arbor music scene. By 1965, Jeep was already heavily involved in the management of a local musical group comprised of Ann Arbor high school students, The Rationals. In 1967, A-Square Records was incorporated, and Jeep made a business of managing, producing, and promoting a host of Michigan bands, including the 3rd Power, All The Lonely People, The Amboy Dukes, The Apostles, Frijid Pink, The Frost, The Jagged Edge, The MC5, The Children, The Rationals, Savage Grace, Shakey Jake, The Scot Richard Case, The Stooges (Jeep is said to have given Iggy Pop his nickname), The Thyme, Wilson Mower Pursuit, and many more.
While there is little doubt that Jeep's passion for the music scene was genuine, he was at best an amateur when it came to business. Before long, the scene he had helped create was beginning to outgrow the small local production companies that had nurtured it. By the early 1970s, A-Squared and other local labels were being pushed out by larger commercial operations. In the summer of 1971, Jeep moved to Boston, where he once again worked for Discount Records. In 1976, Jeep returned to the music business, this time as northeast regional promoter for United Artists. Additionally, while in Boston, Jeep worked with WFNX-FM radio and participated in a music trivia segment called "Stump Jeep." In the late 1980s, Jeep relocated again from Boston to Baltimore, Maryland where he worked with Diamond Comic Distributors, Inc. Jeep passed away on March, 14 1998 from complications due to diabetes.
The Jeep Holland papers date from his youth in the late 1940s up to his death in 1998, and document his personal life, his education, and his career, particularly the record label and production company he founded, A-Square Records. The collection is comprised of the following series: Administrative, Artist Files, Personal Files, Realia, Sound Recordings, and Visual.
Subjects:
A-Square Records.; Amboy Dukes (Musical group); Ann Arbor (Mich.); Apostles (Musical group: Ann Arbor, Mich.); Children (Musical group); East Lansing (Mich.); Frijid Pink (Musical group); Frost (Musical group); Grande Ballroom.; Holland, Jeep, 1943-1998.; MC5 (Musical group); Musicians' contracts.; Pop, Iggy, 1947-; Rationals (Musical group); Record stores.; Rock music.; Rock music festivals.; Rock music--Michigan--1961-1970.; Savage Grace (Musical group); Sound recordings--Production and direction.; SRC (Musical group); Stooges (Musical group); Talent management.; Third Power (Musical group); UP (Musical group); Wilson Mower Pursuit (Musical group)
Subjects - Visual Materials:
Amboy Dukes (Musical group); Apostles (Musical group); Frijid Pink (Musical group); Frost (Musical group); Gibb, Russ, 1931-; Holland, Jeep, 1943-1998.; MC5 (Musical group); Music festivals--United States.; Rationals (Musical group); Rock groups--American.; Rock music festivals.; SRC (Musical group); Stooges (Musical group); Third Power (Musical group); Wilson Mower Pursuit (Musical group)
Subjects - Sound Recordings:
A-Square Records.; Brownsville Station (Musical group); Catfish (Musical group); Commander Cody and His Lost Planet Airmen (Musical group); Holland, Jeep, 1943-1998.; Mr. Curt (Musical group); Paul, Ray.; Plain Brown Wrapper (Musical group); Rain Like the Sound of Trains (Musical group); UP (Musical group)
Genre Terms:
45 rpm records.; Compact discs.; Phonograph records.; Photographs.; Posters.; Scrapbooks.; Sound recordings.
- Administrative
  Administrative (1964-1990, 2 linear feet) documents the conduct of business for A-Square records, and to a lesser extent Discount Records, Universal Artists, and Diamond Comics. The series contains papers dealing with various professional organizations, assorted contracts, professional correspondence, documentation of events, financial records, and papers pertaining to legal counsel, recording studios and talent agencies.
  - American Federation of Musicians
    - Bulletins, 1966-1970 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 1)
    - Directories, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Forms and Contracts, 1964-1969 (Box 1)
  - Contracts, 1967-1970; 4 folders (Box 1)
  - Correspondence
    - Day, Dennis, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Knight, Larry, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
    - Patlow, Jerry (Box 1)
    - Smeltzer, Gary, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
  - Events
    - Ann Arbor Blues Festival, 1970 (Box 1)
    - Detroit Rock Revival, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Kalamazoo Pop Festival, 1969 (Box 1)
    - Miscellaneous Rock Festivals, 1970-1971 (Box 1)
  - Financial Documents
    - Ledgers
      - A-Square Productions, 1967-1970; 4 folders (Box 1)
      - The Apostles, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
      - The Children, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
      - The Frost (Box 1)
      - The Gang, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
      - Jagged Edge, 1968 (Box 1)
      - Shakey Jake, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
      - The Thyme, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
    - Notecards (Box 1)
  - General Files
    - A+A Productions, 1969 (Box 1)
    - American Federation of Television and Radio Artists, 1967 (Box 1)
    - Answering Service, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
    - Argus (Box 1)
    - Buddha Records, 1971 (Box 1)
    - Capitol Records, 1968-1969 (Box 1)
    - Carty's Music, 1967-1969 (Box 1)
    - Cassette Inventory (Box 1)
    - Cavern Records, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
    - Clark Oil, 1968 (Box 1)
    - Copy Art Photographers, 1967-1968 (Box 1)
    - Creem (Box 1)
    - Custom Specialty Advertising, 1967-1970 (Box 1)
    - Diamond Comics, 1989-1990 (Box 1)
    - Discount Photocopy, 1969-1970 (Box 1)
    - Employees (Box 1)
    - Follett Book Store, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
    - Foremost Photographic Service, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
    - Hard Corps Productions, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Hideout Productions, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Holland-London, 1965-1967 (Box 2)
    - Insurance, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Kier Photo Service (Box 2)
    - Mass Photoprint Company, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
    - Master Charge (Box 2)
    - Merit Music, 1968 (Box 2)
    - Michigan Bell Telephone, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
    - Michigan Department of Licensing and Regulation, 1967-1969 (Box 2)
    - Michigan Graphic, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Mobil Oil, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
    - The Music Center, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
    - Music Productions Inc., 1970 (Box 2)
    - New England Telephone, 1971 (Box 2)
    - Office Equipment, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
    - Pulse Productions, 1969-1972 (Box 2)
    - Roach Printing Company, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
    - Scorpio Music, 1970 (Box 2)
    - Steeb Dodge, 1966-1969 (Box 2)
    - Sunn, 1970s (Box 2)
    - Turntables and Tape Recorders, 1968 (Box 2)
    - United Artists
      - Biographies, 1977-1978 (Box 2)
      - Miscellaneous, 1976-1977 (Box 2)
  - Legal Counsel
    - Brignall, James, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
    - Hofer, Walter, 1966-1971 (Box 2)
    - Levy, John, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
  - Recording Studios
    - DXM Recording Studio, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
    - Pioneer Recording Studio, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
    - United Sound Vendors, 1967-1968 (Box 2)
    - Vanguard Records, 1969 (Box 2)
    - Virco Recording Co., 1968-1970 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous Studios, 1968-1969 (Box 2)
  - Signature Authorizations, 1968-1969; 2 folders (Box 2)
  - Talent Agencies
    - American Talent International, 1973 (Box 2)
    - Delta Promotions (Box 2)
    - Diversified Management Agency, 1971-1973 (Box 2)
    - Haganah, 1969-1970 (Box 2)
    - International Famous Agency, 1970-1971 (Box 2)
    - United Artists Biographies, 1977 (Box 2)
    - Windfall Artists, 1970 (Box 2)
  - Venues
    - Grande Ballroom
      - Articles, 1970 (Box 2)
      - Concert Flyers (Box 2)
      - General, 1968-1970 (Box 2)
    - Psychedelic Midway, 1969 (Box 2)
- Artist Files
  Artist Files (1965-1978, 5 linear feet) consists of information regarding a large number of the bands Jeep worked with through his time with A-Square records, as well as Universal Artists and his own personal interests. Individual artist files can contain articles and newspaper clippings, concert flyers, contracts, general papers, photographs, and radio charts.
  - 3rd Power
    - Articles and Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
    - Concert Flyers (Box 3)
    - Contracts, 1968-1970 (Box 3)
    - General, 1968-1970 (Box 3)
    - Photographs
      - Large (Box 3)
      - Small (Box 3)
  - Air Speed Indicator, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Alice Cooper, 1971-1973 (Box 3)
  - All the Lonely People
    - Concert Flyers (Box 3)
    - Contacts, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
    - Photographs (Box 3)
  - Amboy Dukes
    - Articles and Clippings, 1968-1969 (Box 3)
    - General, 1968-1970 (Box 3)
    - Photographs (Box 3)
  - The Apostles
    - Contracts, 1967-1968 (Box 3)
    - General, 1967-1968 (Box 3)
    - Photographs (Box 3)
  - Ashmollyan Quintet, 1968 (Box 3)
  - The Beach Boys, 1971-1973 (Box 3)
  - The Beatles, 1970-1972 (Box 3)
  - Bedlam Riff, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Bhang, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Big Red (Box 3)
  - Blackstone Row, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Blackwood Drake, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Blind Faith, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Blues Train
    - Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
    - General, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Brownsville Station
    - Articles and Clippings, 1970 (Box 3)
    - General, 1970 (Box 3)
    - Photographs (Box 3)
  - Bump, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Butterfield Blues Band (Box 3)
  - Cactus, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Canned Heat, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Carousel, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Caste, 1968-1970 (Box 3)
  - Catfish
    - Articles and Clippings, 1970-1973 (Box 3)
    - Concert Flyers, 1971 (Box 3)
    - General, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
    - Photographs (Box 3)
  - Charging Rhinoceros of Soul, 1968 (Box 3)
  - Chip Stevens Blues, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - The Chosen Few (Box 3)
  - Eric Clapton, 1970 (Box 3)
  - Joe Cocker (Box 3)
  - Commander Cody and his Lost Planet Airmen, 1971-1973 (Box 3)
  - Cream, 1969-1970 (Box 3)
  - Crystal Maze, 1969 (Box 3)
  - Mr. Curt, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
  - Damn Thing, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Dhobi's Itch, 1970 (Box 4)
  - The Doors (Box 4)
  - The Eagles, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Electric Light Orchestra (Box 4)
  - Elephants Memory, 1972 (Box 4)
  - Ellie Pop, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Elvis, 1969-1974 (Box 4)
  - Everlon Nevermore (Box 4)
  - Excels, 1968 (Box 4)
  - Featherstone (Box 4)
  - The Feminine Touch (Box 4)
  - Floating Circus (Box 4)
  - Frijid Pink
    - Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
    - General, 1970 (Box 4)
    - Photographs (Box 4)
    - Radio Charts, 1970 (Box 4)
  - The Frost
    - Articles and Clippings, 1968-1970 (Box 4)
    - Concert Flyers, 1969 (Box 4)
    - Contracts, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    - Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    - General, 1968-1970 (Box 4)
    - Photographs
      - Copy Art (Box 4)
      - Garris, Gordon (Box 4)
      - Hartman, Don (Box 4)
      - Rigg, Bobby (Box 4)
      - Wagner, Dick (Box 4)
      - Group Photos
        - Large (Box 4)
        - Small (Box 4)
    - Radio Charts, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Früt (of the Loom), 1971 (Box 4)
  - The Fugs (Box 4)
  - The Gang
    - Contracts, 1967 (Box 4)
    - General, 1967-1968 (Box 4)
    - Photographs (Box 4)
  - Girls Inc., 1969-1970 (Box 4)
  - Grand Funk Railroad
    - General, 1971 (Box 4)
    - Photographs (Box 4)
  - Guardian Angel, 1971 (Box 4)
  - Happiness Ticket, 1967 (Box 4)
  - Head Over Heels, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Jimi Hendrix, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
  - Hideaways, 1967 (Box 4)
  - HP and The Grass Roots Movement, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
  - Humble Pie (Box 4)
  - Jagged Edge
    - Contracts, 1968 (Box 4)
    - General, 1968-1969 (Box 4)
    - Photographs (Box 4)
  - James Gang, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Julia, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Julius Victor, 1969 (Box 4)
  - KJ Knight and the Knightriders (Box 4)
  - Lighthouse, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Litter, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Luther Black (Box 4)
  - Maend, 1969 (Box 4)
  - Magpye, 1970 (Box 4)
  - The Maxx, 1969-1970 (Box 4)
  - MC5
    - Articles and Clippings, 1968-1972 (Box 5)
    - Concert flyers (Box 5)
    - Contracts, 1967-1969 (Box 5)
    - General, 1967-1969 (Box 5)
    - Photographs
      - Large (Box 5)
      - Small (Box 5)
    - Radio Charts, 1969 (Box 5)
  - McKenna Mendelson Mainline, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Mighty Quick, 1970 (Box 5)
  - Mountain, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
  - Mr. Stress Blues, 1968-1969 (Box 5)
  - The Muffs, 1968 (Box 5)
  - The Nickelplate Express, 1968 (Box 5)
  - The Odds and Ends, 1968 (Box 5)
  - The Ohio Power (Box 5)
  - The Ones, 1967 (Box 5)
  - Orange Fuzz, 1968 (Box 5)
  - Ormandy, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Our Mother's Children
    - Contracts, 1967-1969 (Box 5)
    - General, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
    - Photographs (Box 5)
  - The Pack, 1968-1970 (Box 5)
  - Phenomena, 1969 (Box 5)
  - Plain Brown Wrapper
    - Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
    - General, 1969-1970 (Box 5)
    - Photographs (Box 5)
  - The Prime Movers, 1966 (Box 5)
  - Procol Harum (Box 5)
  - Promise (Box 5)
  - Proud Flesh (Box 5)
  - The Rain, 1967-1968 (Box 5)
  - The Rainmakers, 1967 (Box 5)
  - The Rationals
    - Articles and Clippings, 1966-1970 (Box 5)
    - Concert Flyers (Box 5)
    - Concert Notes (Box 5)
    - General, 1966-1970 (Box 5)
    - Photographs
      - 1967 (Box 5)
      - April 1968 (Box 5)
      - June 1968 (Box 5)
      - General, 2 folders (Box 5)
      - Copy Art (Box 5)
      - Negatives and proof sheets (Box 5)
    - Schedules, 1965-1967 (Box 5)
    - Scot's Pirates, 1992 (Box 5)
    - Set Lists (Box 5)
    - Radio Charts, 1966-1970 (Box 5)
  - Rare Earth, 1970-1972 (Box 6)
  - Rascals, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Lou Rawls (Box 6)
  - Red White and Blues Band
    - Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - General, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Richmond, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
  - Linda Ronstadt, 1971 (Box 6)
  - Rush, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Mitch Ryder (Box 6)
  - St. Louis Union, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Salvage, 1970 (Box 6)
  - The, 1969 (Box 6)
  - Savage Grace
    - Articles and Clippings, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Concert Flyers (Box 6)
    - Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - General, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Photographs (Box 6)
    - Radio Charts, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Scarecrow (Box 6)
  - The Second Rush, 1968 (Box 6)
  - Bob Seger, 1967-1968 (Box 6)
  - Shakey Jake
    - Concert Flyers (Box 6)
    - Contracts, 1968-1970 (Box 6)
    - General, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Small Faces, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Sky
    - Concert Flyers (Box 6)
    - Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - General, 1970 (Box 6)
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Southwind, 1971 (Box 6)
  - SRC (Scott Richards Case)
    - Articles and Clippings, 1967-1970 (Box 6)
    - Blue Scepter (Box 6)
    - Concert Flyers (Box 6)
    - Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - General, 1969-1971 (Box 6)
    - Photographs
      - Large (Box 6)
      - Small (Box 6)
    - Radio Charts, 1967-1969 (Box 6)
  - Cat Stevens, 1967-1973 (Box 6)
  - Stoney and Meatloaf, 1971 (Box 6)
  - The Stooges
    - Articles and Clippings, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Concert flyers (Box 6)
    - Contracts, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
    - Fan club (Box 6)
    - General, 1968-1970 (Box 6)
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Stuart Avery Assemblage (Box 6)
  - Sun
    - Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - General, 1969-1970 (Box 6)
    - Photographs (Box 6)
  - Sunday Funnies, 1969-1971 (Box 6)
  - The Talismen, 1967 (Box 6)
  - Target, 1968-1969 (Box 6)
  - Tate Blues, 1969 (Box 6)
  - The Tea, 1970 (Box 6)
  - Teegarden and VanWinkle
    - Articles and Clippings, 1969-1971 (Box 7)
    - General, 1968-1970 (Box 7)
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Radio charts, 1970 (Box 7)
  - Three Dog Night (Box 7)
  - Thyme
    - Photographs
      - Copy Art (Box 7)
      - General (Box 7)
      - Laminated (Box 7)
      - Negatives (Box 7)
  - Tiers, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
  - The Toad, 1968 (Box 7)
  - Touchstone (Box 7)
  - Tribal Sinfonia, 1970 (Box 7)
  - The Troyes, 1966-1968 (Box 7)
  - Underground Wall, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Unrelated Segments, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
  - The UP
    - Concert flyers (Box 7)
    - Contracts, 1967-1970 (Box 7)
    - General, 1968-1971 (Box 7)
    - Photographs (Box 7)
    - Press Releases, 1969 (Box 7)
  - Virgin Dawn
    - Concert flyers (Box 7)
    - Contracts, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
    - General, 1970 (Box 7)
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Toby Wesselfox, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
  - Whiz Kids, 1971 (Box 7)
  - The Who
    - General, 1969-1975 (Box 7)
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Wilson Mower Pursuit
    - Concert flyers (Box 7)
    - Contracts, 1968-1970 (Box 7)
    - General, 1968-1970 (Box 7)
    - Loy Norrix High School, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Photographs (Box 7)
  - Johnny Winter (Box 7)
  - The Woolies, 1969-1972 (Box 7)
- Personal Files
  Personal Files (Late 1940s/Early 1950s-1998, 2.5 linear feet) are comprised of papers documenting Jeep's personal life. The series includes personal correspondence, general papers, and papers from Jeep's youth such as school assignments, projects, and grades.
  - Correspondence
    - Adcock, Bob, 1968-1969 (Box 7)
    - Alyta, 1961-1962 (Box 7)
    - Anne, 1969 (Box 7)
    - Apple, Jim, 1962 (Box 7)
    - Betsy, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Chase, Tippi, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Cotton, Betty, 1975-1978 (Box 7)
    - Cuthberson, Cynthia, 1961-1962 (Box 7)
    - Fischer, Connie, 1960 (Box 7)
    - Fricker, Bobbi, 1965 (Box 7)
    - High School Friends, 1961 (Box 7)
    - Holland, Francis Jr. (Jomp), 1962 (Box 7)
    - Holiday Cards (Box 7)
    - Kaiser, Jon, 1964-1968 (Box 7)
    - Karen, 1968 (Box 7)
    - Kays, Marilyn, 1961-1962 (Box 7)
    - Kerry, Elaine, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Kessler, Dennis, 1978-1980 (Box 8)
    - Krinkle, 1971-1972 (Box 8)
    - Lucille, 1961-1962 (Box 8)
    - Maggie, 1968-1969 (Box 8)
    - Marsha, 1967-1968 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Parents, 1961-1975 (Box 8)
    - Prochniak, Sue, 1966-1967 (Box 8)
    - Ric, 1969-1970 (Box 8)
    - Sedlarik, Carol, 1967-1969 (Box 8)
    - Sheri, 1969 (Box 8)
    - Simpson, Lynn, 1971-1973 (Box 8)
    - Sivek, Sue, 1970-1972 (Box 8)
    - Stahl, Rick, 1969 (Box 8)
    - Wade, Dianne, 1970-1972 (Box 8)
    - Waz, 1970 (Box 8)
  - General Files
    - Address directory (Box 8)
    - Album collection (Box 8)
    - Alexander, Ice, 1969 (Box 8)
    - Allopenna, Karen, 1971 (Box 8)
    - Bills etc., 1961-1962 (Box 8)
    - Car documents, 1967-1980 (Box 8)
    - Cotton, Betty, 1977 (Box 8)
    - Derlen, Ronnie, 1972 (Box 8)
    - Diamond Comics, 1989-1990 (Box 8)
    - Drawings (Box 8)
    - Eberline, Bill, 1969-1975 (Box 8)
    - Fabulous Furry Freak Brothers (Box 8)
    - "Grit Noise and Revolution" (Box 8)
    - Jordan, Will, 1970-1971 (Box 8)
    - Little Nemo (Box 8)
    - Kaiser, Jon, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
    - Marriage, 1968 (Box 8)
    - McKinney, Sharon, 1969 (Box 8)
    - Memorial
      - General, 1998 (Box 8)
      - Obituaries, 1998 (Box 8)
      - Stories, 1998 (Box 8)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 8)
    - Newspaper clippings, 2 folders (Box 8)
    - Optner, Jim (Box 8)
    - Parents, 1987 (Box 8)
    - Posters (Box 8)
    - Promotional Materials (Box 9)
      - Memorabilia (Box 9)
      - Photographs, etc. (Box 9)
    - Ryder rental, 1971 (Box 9)
    - Simpson, Lynn (Box 9)
    - Standard oil, 1968 (Box 9)
    - Taxes, 1985-1996 (Box 9)
    - Telethons, 1977-1979 (Box 9)
    - Unemployment, 1975-1976 (Box 9)
    - Wetmore, Bruce, 1970-1971 (Box 9)
  - Youth
    - Assorted Event Programs, 1956-1961 (Box 9)
    - Assorted Holiday Cards (Box 9)
    - Boy Scouts, 1953-1955 (Box 9)
    - Camp Al Gon Quian, 1955-1957 (Box 9)
    - Miscellaneous (Box 9)
    - Newspaper Clippings (Box 9)
    - Early childhood artwork, 2 folders (Box 9)
    - Elementary school assignments (Box 9)
    - Junior High School
      - Assignments, 2 folders (Box 9)
      - "Character Book" (Box 9)
      - Newspaper, "East Lansing Junior Highlights,", 1956 (Box 9)
    - High School
      - Assignments (Box 9)
      - Diploma, 1961 (Box 9)
      - Grades, 1957-1959 (Box 9)
      - Graduation, 1961 (Box 9)
      - Graduation Scrapbook, 1961 (Box 9)
      - National Merit Scholars, 1960-1961 (Box 10)
      - Newspaper, "The Trojan Trumpet,", 1955-1956 (Box 10)
      - Posters (Box 10)
      - Yearbooks, 1956; 1957; 1959 (Box 10)
      - Student Council
        - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 10)
        - Meeting Materials, 3 folders (Box 10)
        - Notebooks (Box 10)
    - College
      - Administrative Correspondence, 1963-1966 (Box 10)
      - Grades, 1962-1965 (Box 10)
      - Miscellaneous (Box 10)
      - Newspaper Clippings, 1962 (Box 10)
- Realia
  Realia (Late 1960s-Early 1970s, 1 folder) is comprised of promotional buttons that were made for the various bands Jeep worked with at A-Square.
  - Buttons (Box 10)
- Sound Recordings
  Sound Recordings (1969-1993, .25 linear feet) is comprised primarily of 45 rpm singles from various bands that worked with A-Square Records. Additionally, it contains a CD compilation of songs released on the A-Square label in the late 1960s.
  - A-Square Compilation, 1 optical disks CD-Rs (Box 10)
  - Brownsville Station, 2 phonograph records 45rpm
    - "Rock & Roll Holiday," (B side; "Jailhouse Rock), 1969 (Box 10)
    - "That's Fine," (B side; "Tell Me All About It") (Box 10)
  - Catfish, "Down in the Flood," (B side; "Witchcraft"), 1 phonograph records 45rpm (Box 10)
  - Commander Cody and the Lost Planet Airmen, "Watch My .38," (B side; "Semi-Truck"), 1973; 1 phonograph records 45rpm (Box 10)